davidairey.com 2007-05-02

# David Airey :: Web and Graphic Design :: Edinburgh

This Privacy Statement was last updated on 27 Sept. 2006. 

I understand the value of your personal information and respect your right to privacy. I am committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. This commitment includes protecting the personal information that I obtain from you.

**General:** Unless you provide information voluntarily, I will not collect any personal information about you when you visit [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/). If I ask you to provide information that personally identifies you, my request to do so will be specific. If I want you to provide additional information, I will explain why I need the additional information and how it will be used at the time of the request. 

**E-mail From You:** You may e-mail messages to me that will contain your name and e-mail address along with any additional information you may wish to include in the text of your message. 

**Third-Parties:** Your personal information will not be given to third-parties without your prior consent. If a request to provide your information to a third-party is made you will be given full details as to why this would benefit you.

**CVs/resumés:** I use [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/) as a recruiting tool to provide visitors seeking employment with me the ability to submit CVs/resumés or other personal information. 

**Surveys:** Occasionally, I conduct online surveys on a specific topic. My surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate.

**Website Usage Information:** My web server automatically collects and aggregates information about your visit to [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/), including your IP address, service provider, browser type, domain names of referring websites, operating system, pages accessed on my website, and the date and time of your access. This information is not personally identifiable. I analyze this aggregated information in an effort to optimize your experience and enhance your time spent on my website.

I use your personal information in several ways:

  * To fulfill your requests and process your transactions.
  * To respond to your e-mail messages.
  * To support your customer relationship with me. For example, if you provide me with an e-mail or postal address, you may receive mailings from me with information concerning special offers, new services or products. You can unsubscribe to mailings from me at any time. Please refer to the "Opt-Out" section of this Policy for details on the "opt-out" process.
  * To process responses to employment opportunities posted on [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/). The personal information that is contained in your resume will not be used for any other purpose.
  * To help recognise visitors who have previously made contact through my website.
  * To provide you with marketing materials and sales information about the service I provide. 

I may combine the personal information that I collect from you on my website with other information that you provide to me in connection with your use of my services. 

I occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on my behalf, mainly for delivering purchases, such as printed material. I will only provide such companies with the personal information that they need to deliver the service that I have requested of them. They are prohibited from using the personal information that I provide to them for any other purpose and I make reasonable efforts to ensure that all third parties with whom I share personal information undertake to adhere to this Policy. I do not otherwise share your personal information with third-parties, unless you have granted me permission to do so. 

I may disclose or use your personal information when I, in good faith, believe that either the law requires me to do so or such action is necessary to protect or defend my rights or property. 

I provide reasonable and practical access for you to identify inaccuracies in your personal information. If you provide me with personal information through the David Airey website, you have the right to access this data.

To request an update, modification, or deletion of any personal information maintained by me, you can contact me using the [contact form here](http://www.davidairey.com/contact.php). I will, upon request, update or delete your personal information; however, I will not be able to update or delete data that has been archived as part of my normal business operations (for VAT / tax purposes).

I keep the personal information collected through my website as long as it is required to service your request, or until you request its deletion. I retain aggregated information collected about your visit to my website (i.e., browser type, domain name, pages visited) until I have completed a review and analysis of this information. 

I do not add third-party data to your personal information and maintain your personal information in a merged or supplemented format. 

If you are a personal contact, you may receive direct mail or other marketing material from me. 

At any time, you can "opt-out" of receiving direct mail and marketing material from me, such as product and service updates, by either contacting me using the [contact form here](http://www.davidairey.com/contact.php) or by following the "unsubscribe" instructions contained within the communication.

If at any time in the future I decide to use your personal information for a purpose not currently stated in this Policy, I will modify the Policy to disclose such usage in accordance with Section 8 below. 

Websites accessed from [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/) via hyperlinks or links to other sites may be governed by privacy policies and practices that differ from this Policy. The information practices of other third-party websites linked to [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/) are not covered by this Policy. You are encouraged to become familiar with the privacy policies and practices of every website you visit prior to disclosing any personal information.

Information posted to discussion forums, bulletin boards, chat rooms and other public forums may be displayed publicly. Please consider this before posting. 

I store your personal information in a secure location that is accessible only me. I make reasonable efforts to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. In addition, I use a secure server to protect the safety and security of transactions over the Internet involving personal information. 

I may modify or amend this Policy from time to time. In an effort to keep you informed of changes to this Policy, I will indicate the effective date of the currently posted policy at the top of the Policy. For substantial changes to this Policy, I will notify you by placing prominent notice on my homepage. Changes to this Policy will not affect my use of previously provided personal information. No personal information provided by you under the terms of this Policy (or any prior version of this Policy) will be used in a manner that is materially inconsistent with it, without your prior written permission.

By using [www.davidairey.com](http://www.davidairey.com/), you signify your acceptance of this Policy, as amended from time to time in accordance with Section 8 above. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions contained in this Policy, please do not use this website. 

If you have thoughts, questions or suggestions about this Privacy Policy Statement or any other aspect of your relationship with me, please contact me [using the form here](http://www.davidairey.com/contact.php).

**Write:**  
David Airey   
9 Edina Place   
Edinburgh  
Scotland  
EH7 5RN

[Back to the top](http://www.davidairey.com/privacy.php).
